Nir and Gali Present
Company Life
Candles Lighting
Hanukka Song Lyrics
Wow, They killed me with this,
How (badly) I want it
Come on, why is it here, Take one, Happy Holiday!
No, I am keeping myself, are you normal?
Yalla, Holiday,
This goes directly to the butt
Yalla, holiday
Yalla, fuck it, holiday
Hello, good evening. - Good evening.
Welcome. What is the name?
Sufgi (sounds like doughnut)
Nice to meat you, I am Moshik
Welcome to the stomach
Your first checkpoint on your road
Where, are you headed, if I may ask?
Going to the butt
Ok, Ok
Because of any special reason?
Did you hear that it is nice over there?
I (don't) know... My family is there - Yes...
My friends are there, Going to the butt
Yes...
Can I just have a moment of your time, before?
Yalla, nu, quickly
So, as I mention, I am Moshik
Generally speaking, I am the Enzyme in charge here
On the metabolism topic
did you hear about metabolism already?
Do you know the term?
Familiar (with it), yes
Not, not a pro
Metabolism means something very simple
Every material that enters the body, breaks down
Absorbed in the body, and helps the different systems
Ok
Vegtables and fruits are giving us vitamines
Proteins help us building the muscles
Complex carbonshydrates are giving us
Available energy for the daily activity
And once in a while, arriving to the body,
the so called "empty" carbonhydrates
with plenty of saturated fat
Who tend to break down more, and even accumulate
in places like the belly, the thighs
The butt. - yes, also... also the posterior
Now, towards the holiday, we started here with a new initiative
Everyone breaks down - everyone contributes
From now pn - also simpler carbonhydrates will break down,
Will give available energy to the body
and this way, we will keep a more esthetic enviorment
a healthier enviorment, that is fun to live in to all of us
I am going to the butt, I don't get it
But, did you understand our initiative?
Did you understand the importance?
I think so, yes.
And a will to contribute, exists in you?
A will to help the community, to help
To give from yourself, is there in you?
Do you have this will?
There is jam in me, what, you are "falling" on me
Going to the butt. move.
Wait a sec, Sufgi - move
Lets take a moment for breathing. = please move
Sufgi, silly you, what are you doing here?
Nothing, this wierdo fell on me
Hello, good evening to you
Shut up, Shut up,
Tell me, are you (not) Normat
There is, like, half a plate on it's way
Yalla, quickly to the butt
Let's catch a seat
What chick are you - right one
cool ("bomb") - we are together
Moment, can I have a minute of your time?
Get off me
We are going to the butt, stop it
Friends, wait a moment!
At least maybe go to the boobs?
Oh dear
Yallaaaa, to the buttttttt
No, No, this isn't heappening
Yallaaaaa, to the buttt - guys, wait a sec!
A minute from your time. - Yalllaaa to the butttt
Yallaaaa, to the buttttttt
Good evening
Are you shitting me
Subtitles - Kali