This one is for you
today
you surprised me Noni
Viva la "tape"
how is "cutie"?
Roi?
What? - ok,
I am arriving late today
so the showers and everything - you are doing on your own
Will you manage?
Bye
Roi?
also I will, maybe,
If mommy is not at home
Ra pa pa pa
I am shitting
With an opened door
Oh my baby
Don't stress me out
Give (me) a second
to enjoy from the juice
Resist!
I resist!
To orange juice
With (fruit) pieces
Come on - I didn't come to eat
(I) only want to drink
If mommy is not at home
Ra pa pa pa
I build a camp
In the sofa
Again you fell asleep intead of watching out
The enemy is attacking here for an hour already
Resist!
I Resist!
To orange juice
With (fruit) pieces
Come on I didn't come to eat
(I) Only want to drink!
Going crazy
(I) Don't know
How to "swallow" the hit (the pain)
It is not pleasant to me
It *is* tasty to me
Who is doing "a jackpot" on me (earning on my expanse)
I...
Resist
"How" resist (Resist so much)
To orange juice
With (fruit) pieces
Come on, I didn't come to eat
Only want to drink